その力に魅せられた すごい奴らがいる 「未知」という言葉が放つ魔力
Once someone comes out,
follow their directions.
君が　もっと倒しがいのある 使い手に育つまで…。
Strategy x And x Scheme
今みたいに　僕の顔に
There are more people this time.
それまで そのプレートは　君に預ける。
I wonder if there's anyone I know.
ゲレタに奪われたプレートを
We've undergone some hellish training.
ヒソカの手によって 返されるという 屈辱を味わったゴン
Our teamwork is perfect now.
そして　キルアは…
Thank you for coming!
時間の無駄だぜ。 いくら　つけ回しても 俺は　隙なんか見せないよ。
This year, 1,489 applicants
have made it this far, but the Phase Two examiner has asked me
to trim that number to about 300.
フフフ…
As for the exam... There are two hours before lunch.
もっと怯えろ　もっと憔悴しろ
Defeat five people before then.
俺は慎重な男
Grab their tags when you defeat them, and see me when you have all five.
たとえ相手が子供だろうと 全力を尽くす
I'll wait on the other side of the door. Got it?
あいつが完全に疲労し 眠りに落ちた時…
As soon as I shut the door, you may start.
フッフッフッフッ… 俺は慎重な男！
Every stage of the exam should be like this...
はぁ　来ないなら こっちから行くよ。
You've gotta be strong to be a Hunter.
ホント　嫌なんだよなぁ。 どうせ倒したって １点だろうしさぁ。
Oh, you're here! Killu—
戦うか？
He's totally out of our league...
負けないだろ？ いくら何でも　相手はガキだ
So that's what it takes to
become a top Hunter...
しかし… 何なんだ？　あいつの余裕 よほど腕に自信が？
This will be the last time I
attempt the Hunter Exam...
いったん逃げ… いや　この場を離れるんだ！
We finally have our first applicant.
しかし…
That took an hour and a half.
そんなことしたら 兄ちゃん達に叱られる
What happened to everyone else? They're all asleep.
こいつから プレート　奪っておかないと やっぱり叱られる！
It took me a while to collect all their tags.
兄ちゃん！ おっ。
Is there going to be a second stage?
ん？ あ？
That won't be necessary. He's demonstrated his skill.
あっ　あぁ…。
Killua, denizen of the darkness...
バカか　お前！
He's returned much stronger.
あんなガキ１人も倒せねえのか！
Applicant 1219, Killua-kun.
ち…　違うよ！　アモ兄ちゃん。 何が違うんだよ。
Yeah. You've passed
こ…　子供を痛めつけても かわいそうだろ？
the Hunter Exam!
ウソつけ！　この！
Welcome back, Killua.
わ…　分かったよ！
How was the exam?
兄ちゃん達が そんなに言うなら仕方ないぜ。
I passed it in no time, naturally. Yay!
やってやるよ。
Sorry to interrupt your celebration,
but look at these spell cards.
たとえ俺が 負けそうになっても
Wow...
その時は 兄ちゃん達が助けてくれる
There's even an S-rank card! How much can we sell it for? Oh, let's go ask around!
なぁ　坊ず　プレートくれねえか？
No, we should use it wisely. So what should we do?
おとなしくよこせば　何もしない。
Well, I guess it's safe to hold on to it.
バカ。
With all these defensive spells, we don't need to worry
about it getting stolen.
ああ　言わんこっちゃない へへっ　バッチリみぞおち。
If you have all these cards,
you should use them... Start by using this one.
ありゃあ　地獄だぜ。
You can choose a player you've
met before, and talk to them. Contact
Communicate with one target
player (encountered within the
game) via your Book.
(Connection maintained for
a maximum of 3 minutes.
May only be broken by
player who used this card.)
[LR][NORM]
よっと。
Who should we talk to?
えっ？
We won't know until we see who's available.
何だ？　手加減してやったのかぁ？
Contact on!
１９８番か。
Oh, I see a lot of names.
えっ？　ウソ？　あっ…。
Hey, Gon...
俺の欲しい番号と １番違いってことは
When did you run into him? Huh?
もしかして１９９番は そっちの２人の　どっちかかな。
Chrollo Lucilfer Chrollo?
ウモリ。
I haven't seen Chrollo inside the game.
ああ。
Does that mean you guys passed
each other without noticing?
フォーメーションだ マジで行く。
Huh? What are you talking about? That doesn't make sense.
こいつは　ただのガキじゃねえ。
Kurapika sealed his Nen. Yeah, and you have to use
Nen to enter the game.
こいつが　どれだけの腕を 持っていようが
Sorry about that. Chrollo Lucilfer This probably isn't the boss.
俺達の連携攻撃には 勝てないはずだ
He hasn't purged the Nen from his body.
俺達３兄弟は
Purging Nen?
このフォーメーションで どんな強い相手でも倒して来た
It's very doable. Seriously? Of course!
今に見てろ お前をズタズタにしてやるぜ
If you can place Nen on others, it's not unreasonable to think
Nen can be removed, as well. Does that mean Chrollo has removed
Kurapika's Nen, and entered the game?
上！
I'll leave the game real quick. You can use a spell card to leave.
あっ。 動かないでね。
Save it. I can be out and back in four hours.
俺の指 ナイフより　よく切れるから。
I should have realized this sooner...
うっ　うっ…。
Yorknew City                                        Greed Island This island is directly east of Yorknew City.
あれ　こっちは１９７番かぁ。
East is the direction to go.
もう俺って　こういう勘は すっげぇ鈍いんだよなぁ。
You will find one who awaits you. I see.
ねぇ　あんたが１９９番？
So the boss came here to find
someone to purge that Nen.
ああ。 ちょうだい。
The boss arrived the same way we did, but then Razor kicked him out.
くっ…。
That was when he realized
this was Greed Island.
サンキュ さて　いらないプレートは…。
But since the boss can't use Nen, he can't enter the island
via the usual channels. So he must have hired someone
to come to this island for him.
あっ　あっ…。
The one who can purge this
Nen is on Greed Island.
今度は　こっち！
Change in plans again...
あと３日あるし 頑張って捜しなよ。
I have a small correction.
じゃあな！
You're...
あぁ…。 クソ！
Hisoka! It was my idea to use Chrollo's name.
フッ…　１９７番は
I'm dying to kill you right here and now, but I'll let the boss do that.
いつも　１９９番と 一緒に行動していたからな。
Well, if anything comes up,
use Contact to get in touch.
まさか　あの小僧が 片付けてくれるとは 思わなかったが
If I learn anything new, I'll let you know.
しばらく 様子を見ていて正解だったな。
Bye.
おかげで楽にプレートを手に… えっ？
So the boss hired Hisoka...
うっ　うぅ…。
He probably didn't have much
choice, but it's still weird. And his reward is probably a duel,
once the boss is cleansed.
あの小僧　気づいていたのか…。
But now, it's only a matter of time until the boss comes back!
不覚。
I doubt it. I would know at once
ああ　つまんねえなぁ。 ゴンの奴　何やってっかなぁ。
if Nen I placed on a spider
had been removed. So when you chose your power, you
knew something like this might happen? Of course... If you're able to place Nen on others, it only makes sense to assume
ヒソカに会ってから４日 誰も見つけられなかったな。
What should I do? It'll be fine. Let me handle... What could you possibly know?
ああ。
You have no idea what's going
to happen to us now!
一度　スタート地点に 戻ってみるか？ ん？
Neon... I need Neon!
もしかしたら
Restore Neon at once!
もう合格者が 出ちまってるかもしれないぜ。 いや　それは　ない。
Damn! Why did this happen?
仮に　いったん プレートを奪われたとしても
I wonder what's wrong...
また　奪い返すチャンスがあるのが ４次試験の特徴だ。
Why did it stop working?
逆にいえば ６点分のプレートを集めても
See ya.
今度は　それを期日まで 守らねばならない。 この試験に　早抜けは　ないのさ。
Looks like it's not the real Chrollo.
そうか…。 だが　行ってみる価値はある。
Oh... Kurapika was pretty calm about it.
あと　たった１日　すでに６点分の プレートを集めた者なら
Like he wasn't concerned or just didn't care. Well, it sounds like you
got worried for nothing.
少しでもゴールに近い所で 様子を見たくなるのが心理だろう。
Now it's time to focus on yourselves. Osu!
私が　そうだからな。
Start with the basics... We're not going to train.
あっ…。
It's time to start
よし　行ってみよう。
beating this game!
どうだ？　誰かいるか？ いや…。 さすがに　すぐに見つかるような 場所には　いないな。
First comes rock! Rock, paper... Rock!
クソっ。
Wow!
落ち合う場所と時間を決めて
It's raining bugs!
２人　バラバラで探したほうが 効率がいいな。
Found it. Difficulty rank A!
ああ。
King Great White Beetle
A legendary insect that
releases pheromones
which attract other insects
to start a massive colony.
Can only leave the colony
for brief evening walks.
３人のほうが もっといいでしょ？
That's three King Great White Beetle cards!
ゴン！ ゴン！
You could've gotten more if
you'd thrown a real punch.
やっぱり　みんな考えることは 一緒だね。
Well, I didn't want to damage the tree.
上で見てたら　他にも何人か この近くに来てたよ。
There is no such girl in this mansion.
マジか？　そっか 上から探せばよかったのか。
Even if there were, it would be impossible
無理無理　ゴンの視力があって 初めてできる芸当だ。
for you to bypass all the traps and find her. Found her.
ゴン！ ん？
She was in a hidden room,
four floors underground.
お前は　もう プレートを集めたのか？
What? Curse you!
うん…　まぁね。
Got an A-rank Gold Dust Girl! Gold Dust Girl
A girl who releases golden dust.
One bath a day will net approx. 500 G.
Very shy and quiet.
クソっ　じゃあ　俺だけかよ まだ点数が足りないのは。
The guard was a rank F.
レオリオのターゲットは？
Next, let's head to the
City of Gambling, Dorias!
２４６番のポンズって女だ。
Wait, wasn't today supposed to be
薬と名のつくものは 何でも扱う奴らしい。
the monthly contest in Antokiba? We'll be passing through, so let's give it a go.
ゴン　上から見つけた奴の中に 女は　いなかったか？
Our winner is the Killua and Gon team.
いなかった。 そっか…。
Paladin's Necklace
When a player wears this,
all spells targeting player
will be reflected.
Can also dispel curses
placed on any card
touched by player. A Paladin's Necklace! Score!
大ざっぱに考えられるのは　４つ。
I don't understand this description.
「彼女が無事で プレートを持っている」。
We can ask one of the shopkeepers.
「無事だが プレートは奪われてしまった」。
When you wear this necklace, you can reflect all attack spells.
「彼女は無事ではないが プレートは持っている」。
And if you touch cards under the
「無事ではなく　プレートもない」。 無事でないのに　プレートを 持ってるなんて可能性　あるのか？
effects of Transform or Fake, you can restore them to their original state. Wow...
突発的な事故で動けないとか 誰かにやられたが
If we wear this, we won't have to
worry about losing any cards.
プレートは隠してある パターンなどが考えられる。
Memory Helmet... Memory Helmet
A player will always remember
everything seen or heard
while wearing this item.
Unfortunately, helmet is
very large and heavy. Witch's Love Potion. Witch's Love Potion
If player kisses a pill before
feeding it to a target, target will
become beholden to player.
Each pill will remain effective
for one week. Each bottle
contains 500 pills.
もしも　プレートだけ どこかに隠して
Risky Dice. Risky Dice
A 20-sided die. One side says
Bad Luck, while the other nineteen
say Good Luck. If player rolls
Good Luck, something good will
happen. But if player rolls Bad Luck,
something bad will happen to cancel
out everything that was good.
本人が　もう死んでいるなら プレートは見つけようがないがな。
King Great White Beetle. King Great White Beetle
A legendary insect that
releases pheromones
which attract other insects
to start a massive colony.
Can only leave the colony
for brief evening walks. Gold Dust Girl. Gold Dust Girl
A girl who releases golden dust.
One bath a day will net approx. 500 G.
Very shy and quiet. Paladin's Necklace
When a player wears this,
all spells targeting player
will be reflected.
Can also dispel curses
placed on any card
touched by player. Paladin's Necklace.
どんどん　絶望的になって来たぜ。
A total of six different restricted slot cards!
ねぇ　他にポンズって人の特徴は？
Piece of cake! Piece of cake? Not in the least.
レオリオみたいに 特別な香水をつけてるとか。 あっ。 あっ　そうだ。
This was only possible because you
underwent that grueling training.
ゴンなら　においを 追跡できるかもしれない。 しかし　相手が香水をつけてるとは 限らねえだろ？
Another player has used Contact to reach you.
薬品の　においさ。 あっ。
Yo. It's been a while, Gon. Who are you?
敵は　あらゆるタイプの薬を 使うんだろ？
You don't remember me?
中には　強いにおいを放つものも あるんじゃないのか？ どうだ？　ゴン。 うん　やってみる。
Do you remember the player who took the Sword of Truth
from you in Antokiba? What do you want?
そのために来たんだから。
Up for a trade? I have #66, Witch's Diet Pill,
and #17, VIP Multi-Pass.
ここなのか？　ゴン。 うん　間違いないよ。
We'll give you Patch of Forest, Hidden Hollow
Upon entering and exiting hollow,
player will be transported to a
desolate location. However, player can
return to original location
without spending any money. Hidden Hollow, Palmtop Dragon
As the name implies, this dragon
fits on your palm. Willingly obeys
its master. If raised lovingly,
it can learn to speak. and Palmtop Dragon.
どうする？ もちろん　俺が行く。
And you only have to give us Night Jade,
not Breath of Archangel.
２人は　ここで待っててくれ。
We'd be giving you one SS-rank
card and two S-rank cards, while you'd only give up one A-rank card.
罠らしきものは　ねえな…
Meaning that he thinks he can obtain a Breath of Archangel.
中まで行ってみる。 俺が　いいって言うまで 中には入るなよ。
Does that mean they've assembled
all forty spell card types? It's possible.
３０分だ。 ん？
So they're waiting for Gain to be
used on a Breath of Archangel.
３０分経って連絡がなければ 我々も入るぞ。 うん。 ダメだ。
Night Jade
A jewel blessed by the devil.
When the holder is in danger,
peril will be shifted to another. On the other hand, Night Jade is a card that we monopolized through hard work.
その時は　お前らだけ スタート地点に戻れ。 それはダメだ。
If one of the cards were to be destroyed, one of our jade jewels would
automatically turn into a card.
同盟を組んだ以上 見捨てるわけにはいかないからな。
Which means the A-rank
Night Jade is much harder
じゃあ　同盟は破棄だ。
for them to get than the
SS-rank Breath of Archangel.
協力してもらって 勝手な言い分だが
This is a gamble.
ここからは　１人でやる。
Witch's Love Potion
If player kisses a pill before
feeding it to a target, target will
become beholden to player.
Each pill will remain effective
for one week. Each bottle
contains 500 pills.
ヤダ！ 何だと!?　こら！
VIP Multi-Pass
Present this pass to gain
entry into any location.
Contains 1000 passes.
俺達が　勝手に残ってるんだ！
Book.
それなら　文句ないでしょ？
See ya.
勝手にしろ。
That was uneventful. Kind of disappointing.
預けるぜ。
But now we've gathered
seven types, in three days! We're making decent progress.
うん。
Okay, let's keep this up.
ここは　行くしかねえよな
You have a 0.01% chance of winning. That's one in ten thousand tries. So it all comes down to luck.
ひょっとして…
Awesome! One try!
あなたのターゲットは　私？
Rainbow Diamond
A diamond that glitters like
a rainbow. If this diamond
is presented when proposing,
you will never be turned down. A Rainbow Diamond! Score!
ポンズ！
That's what I thought...
意味ないよ
This die is the key to winning in this city.
ここで　あなたと私が戦っても…。 俺には大ありだぜ。
But if you roll Bad Luck, it could be scary.
お前の言う通り　俺のターゲットは ポンズ　お前だからな。
Don't worry. It can't kill me...
はぁ　あり得ないけど
Oh, no! A slot machine exploded!
百万歩譲って あなたが勝ったとしても
I knew something was wrong.
あなたは　ここから出られない。
That guy hit the jackpot five times in a row. And he was acting weird...
何？　どういうことだ。
He kept rolling a funny-looking die. Yikes, his face is mush...
遅いね　大丈夫かな？　レオリオ。
Roll. S-Spare me...
ああ　もうじき　約束の３０分だ。
This is only your third time. You'll be fine.
クラピカ！　ゴン！ 来るな！
I-I know someone who got
Bad Luck on the first roll and died! If I roll Bad Luck, I'll be hit for every Good Luck
that the other players rolled!
レオリオ！
Come on...
何で…　入って来やがった。
See? It's pretty rare to get Bad Luck.
全身を噛まれている 毒蛇だとしたら…
Now we use the Lottery card.
ツチハブの一種だよ！ １匹の毒は そんなに強くないと思う。 でも　噛まれた数が多過ぎる。
We want #75, Lucky Alexandrite. If you obtain one, we'll set you free.
ペッ。
C-Come on...
うっ…　やめろ…。
Lottery on!
口の中に　虫歯や傷があったら…。
Well?
心配いらない！
#76!
レオリオ！　この中に血清は？
So close! Your luck sucks.
あったら… せめて　お前らだけでも 助けられたのに…　な…　うっ…。
Okay, one more time! Hey, hey, hey, hey! Time for Motarike-kun to
show us what he's got!
レオリオ！ とにかく止血を。
No good, huh?
うん！
Hey, Gen.
これで　よし。 早く医者に診せないと。
I already told you that combat
should be our last resort. It's too early for that.
うん。
No, we're trying to stay
one step ahead of them.
やめたほうがいいわよ。
Though, once we commit, further negotiation will be impossible.
ここからは出られないわ。 どういうことだ？ 一度　この洞窟に入った者が ここから出ようとすると…。
What do you have in mind? We use Tax Collector's Gauntlet, combined with Risky Dice. I understand.
蛇が襲って来る仕掛け。 なっ!? あっ!?
We use this to steal eight cards
from them immediately... But it's definitely dangerous. If someone rolls Bad Luck, they'll probably die.
噛まれたら最後
But this job is too important to leave to them.
彼のように 動くことさえできなくなって
We can do this! We've come this far.
Let's clear the game.
いずれ　死ぬ。
Hey, Gen...
バーボン！
I've told you this many times.
お前の望みは　プレートだろ！ プレートなら全て渡す！ 今すぐ私達を　ここから出せ！
When taking a risk, we three share the danger.
し…　死んでる？
Okay, you have a deal.
蛇遣いバーボンの罠に　はまり
I said I can do this, so I'm gonna do it!
洞窟から出られなくなった ゴン達
Okay, let's move on to the next city!
ハンター試験は？ そして　毒蛇に噛まれた レオリオの運命は？
Gon's team has begun
working to beat the game. The story is nearing its climax.